Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 1490. A speech about Jihad and a sermon about the Iraqi occupation of Kuwait, Circa 1990-2000; 1 (Box 1490)
  ?????????: ????? ????????? ?? ??????? ?????? ? ?????? ???????. ??? ????? ????? 45:32 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 48:13 ?????. ???????: ??? ????????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ???
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ???? ??? ???????? ?????? ??? ???? ????????? ????????? ?? ??????? ??????? ??? ???????. ?? 24:24 ????? ????? ?? ????? ????? ??? ??? ??????? ?? ????? ??? ??? ? ??? ???? ???? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1491. Anthems on Jihad, 1999; 1 (Box 1491)
  Comments: Side A 23:50 min. Side B 24:40 min.
  Side A: A recording of several speakers who chant anthems about warfare, Jihad, and martyrdom in Afghanistan.
  Side B: The same speakers chant anthems about warfare, Jihad, and martyrdom in Afghanistan.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 23:50 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 24:40 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ???? ?? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ??????, ??????, ???????? ?? ?????????
  ????? ??????: ??? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ??????, ??????, ???????? ?? ?????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1494. A sermon about laughing and crying, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1494)
  Comments: Side A 22:53 min. Side B 23:02 min.
  Side A: A speaker talks about laughing and tells stories about the Prophet's laughter in certain situations. The speaker believes that chuckling is forbidden in Islam based on Hadiths narrated in the books of some Salafi scholars such as Ah?mad ibn H?anbal.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about crying and tells stories about crying of the Prophet's companions in certain situations. The speaker reviews Hadiths narrated in the books of some Salafi scholars. From 20:38 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura Qa?f 19-31.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 22:53 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 23:02 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ????? ? ???? ????? ?? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ??????? ???? ?? ??????? ???????? ??? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ??? ??? ????? ??????? ??? ???? ?? ????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ? ???? ????? ?? ????? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ?????. ?????? ??????? ??? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ??? ??? ????? ???????. ?? 20:38 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ? ????? 19 ??? 31
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1495. A sermon on faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1495)
  Comments: Side A 45:33 min. Side B 45:24 min.
  Side A: A speaker talks about the faith in God and its definition according to the Islamic perspective. The speaker recites and interprets many verses from the Qur?a?n about faith.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 45:33 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:24 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ??????? ????? ? ?????? ????? ??????? ????????. ???? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ?????? ?? ???????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ??????? ??????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1496. A poetry reading, Circa 1994-2000; 1 (Box 1496)
  Comments: Audio quality is poor but intelligible. Side A 46:58 min. Side B 46:51min.
  Side A: A recording of a poetry reading in which several speakers read poems about martyr and in praise of Salma?n al-?Awdah.
  Side B: The speakers read poems about Jihad and in praise of Salma?n al-?Awdah.
  ?????????: ????? ??????? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 46:58 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:51 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ????? ???? ???? ??? ??????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ????? ?? ??? ????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ????????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ????? ?? ??? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1497. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1497)
  Comments: The language used is modern standard Arabic and the Gulf dialect. Side A 42:37 min. Side B 44:56 min.
  Side A: The recording is faint and audio is unintelligible. From 20:30 a recording of religious anthems.
  Side B: A recording of a sermon in which a speaker talks about ?Umar ibn ?Abd al-?Azi?z and tells stories about his piety and fairness.
  ?????????: ????? ????????? ?? ??????? ?????? ? ?????? ????????. ??? ????? ????? 42:37 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:56 ?????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ???? ?????? ??? ?????. ?? 20:30 ????? ??????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ??? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ???? ????? ?? ???? ? ????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1498. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1498)
  Comments: Side A 30:56 min. Side B 31:32 min.
  Side A: A recording of a speaker who to talks in unknown language. The recording includes recitation of various verses from the Qur?a?n.
  Side B: A recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura Saba? 1-46. From 14:50 a recording of a speaker who talks in unknown language.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:56 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:32 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ???? ????? ???? ??? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? ?????? ?? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ??? ????? 1 ??? 46. ?? 14:50 ????? ???? ????? ???? ??? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1499. Interpretation of Hadiths, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1499)
  Comments: Side A 21:32 min. Side B 21:33 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he reviews and interprets Hadiths from S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?.
  Side B: The same speaker re views and interprets more Hadiths from S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 21:32 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 21:33 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ??????? ?????? ???? ?????? ????? ????? ??? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ?????? ??????? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ???? ??????? ? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1500. A sermon about loyalty to Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1500)
  Comments: Side A 36:57min. Side B 36:47min. Speaker: ?Abd al-Wahha?b ibn Na?s?ir al-T?urayri?.
  Side A: The speaker gives a sermon in which he talks about investing human resources and capacities to serve the Islamic religion. The speaker tells stories about the role of the Prophet's companions such as Abu? Dharr al-Ghifa?ri? in serving Islam in its beginnings.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about loyalty to Islam and tells stories about the loyalty of a number of the Prophet's companions such as Ka?b ibn Ma?lik and Abi? Mih?jan al-Thaqafi?.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 36:57 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 36:47 ?????. ???????: ??? ?????? ?? ???? ???????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ????? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ? ??????? ??????? ????? ????? ???????? ????? ????? ?? ??? ????? ?????? ??? ??? ?? ??????? ?? ???? ?????? ????????? ?? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ? ???? ??????? ????? ?? ???? ??? ????? ?????? ??? ??????? ??? ??? ?? ???? ? ??? ???? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1501. Religious anthems, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1501)
  Comments: Audio quality is very poor. Side A 27:34 min. Side B 26:23 min.
  Side A: A recording of religious anthems.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ????? ????. ??? ????? ????? 27:34 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 26:23 ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1502. A recording of anthems, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1502)
  Comments: Audio quality is very poor. Side A 45:25 min. Side B 47:33 min.
  Side A: Various and discontinued recordings of speakers who chant anthems about loyalty to H?ama?s, warfare, and revolution.
  Side B: A recording of speakers who chant anthems about warfare and Jihad.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ????? ????. ??? ????? ????? 45:25 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 47:33 ?????
  ????? ?????: ??????? ?????? ? ?????? ???? ?? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????, ??????, ? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1503. Unknown language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1503)
  Comments: Side A 25:36 min. Side B 24:36 min.
  Side A: A recording of speakers who talk in an unknown language.
  Side B: A recording of speakers who talk in an unknown language.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 25:36 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 24:36 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Associated material, Circa 1965-2000 (Box 1504)
  Associated materials consists of original inserts (unsorted and not identified with tape number) and photocopies of audiocassettes.